kickresume.com 2019-07-02

# Kickresume | Privacy policy

### Do we use cookies?

Cookies are small bits of data which get stored on your computer. This information usually isn’t enough to directly identify you, but it allows us to deliver a page tailored to your particular needs and preferences.

We use them to:

  * Keep you signed in
  * Remember information you gave us about you, so you don’t have to give it to us every single time you stop by. Like your cookies preferences
  * Understand how do you use our services, so we can make them better and provide you with personalized content
  * Uniquely identify your browser and internet device, thanks to which we and our partners can target you with discounts to our service, ads and specialized content

You can change your Kickresume **cookie settings** at any time.

There are different types of cookies: 

#### Necessary cookies

Without these cookies our website wouldn’t function and they cannot be switched off. We need them to provide services that you’ve asked for. 

Want an example? We use these cookies when you sign in to Kickresume. We also use them to remember things you’ve already done, like text you’ve entered into a registration form so it’ll be there when you go back to the page in the same session.

We are using our own cookies in addition to NewRelic, PayPal, Ziprecruiter, Google Analytics, Tapfiliate, Hotjar.

#### Performance cookies

Thanks to these cookies, we can count visits and traffic sources to our pages. This allows us to measure and improve the performance of our website and provide you with content you’ll find interesting.

Performance cookies let us see which pages are the most and least popular, and how you and other visitors move around the site. 

If you don’t let us use these cookies, you’ll leave us in the dark a bit, as we won’t be able to give you the content you may like. 

We are using Mixpanel, Intercom, Sentry, ProfitWell.

#### Functional cookies

These cookies allow us to provide you with better functionality and personalization. They may be set up by us or by third party providers whose services we’ve added to our pages. 

The purpose of these cookies is to give you a more personalized experience, based on your previous visits and choices. If you don’t wish to allow these cookies, these services may not work.

Specifically, we are using Sumo, LinkedIn.

#### Marketing cookies 

We use these cookies to uniquely identify your browser and internet device. Thanks to them, we and our partners can build a profile of your interests, and target you with discounts to our service and specialized content.

On the other hand, these cookies allow some companies target you with advertising on other sites. This is to provide you with advertising that you might find interesting, rather than with a series of irrelevant ads you don’t care about. 

Specifically, we are using Google Adwords, Bing Ads, Facebook Ads, LinkedIn Ads, Doubleclick. 

After 12 months we’ll ask for your consent again or you can delete cookies anytime in your browser. Feel free to contact us if you want to know more.

### Controller’s Information concerning the personal data processing

in accordance with the regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 , the General Data Protection Regulation on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation) (hereinafter the GDPR) and the Act No. 18/2018 Coll. on the protection of personal data and on the alteration and amendment of some acts as amended

  1. #### Controller’s Identification data

    1. Your personal data are being processed by the Controller:

**Kickresume s.r.o.** , having its registered address at: 148 Beckov 916 38, Slovak Republic, Identification No.: 48 073 962, registered with the Commercial Register kept by the District Court Trenčín, Section: Sro, Entry No.: 31419/R (hereinafter referred to as the “Controller”). The email of the Controller: [hello@kickresume.com](mailto:hello@kickresume.com)

  2. #### Purpose

    1. Your personal data is processed within the “kickresume” personal data filing system through an online platform operated on the domain kickresume.com.

    2. From the personal data provided by you, our system will create a CV, Cover letter or Personal website with the graphic design of your choice.

    3. We process your personal data for the purposes of carrying out the agreement existing between us based on your decision to engage our services (legal basis: the performance of a contract in accordance with Article 6 (1) (b) of the GDPR).

    4. We also process your personal data for the purposes of understanding how our services are used and how we can improve them (by, in particular, analysing personal data we collected, making statistics) (legal basis: legitimate interest (in evaluating, developing and improving our services, products and systems) in accordance with Article 6 (1) (f) of GDPR).

    5. On the basis of your consent granted through ticking the relevant tick box, you agree that your personal data may be used for the purposes of direct marketing and sending newsletters containing information of special offers or new products (legal basis: consent in accordance with Article 6 (1) (a) of the GDPR). You always have the right to withdraw the consent provided for such purpose by sending an email to: [hello@kickresume.com](mailto:hello@kickresume.com).

    6. On the basis of your consent granted through ticking the relevant tick box, you agree that your personal data may be provided to: (i) partner employers and/or (ii) job recruitment agencies, with which the Controller has concluded an agreement, for the purposes of approaching you with job offers (legal basis: consent in accordance with Article 6 (1) (a) of the GDPR). You always have the right to withdraw the consent provided for such purpose by sending an email to: [hello@kickresume.com](mailto:hello@kickresume.com).

  3. #### List of your personal data

The Controller processes in particular the following categories of your personal data:

Title, name, surname, address of permanent residence, delivery address, email address, phone number, date of birth, gender, age, marital status, information on the education, achieved degrees, courses attended, lectures, certificates or licenses, information on the membership in associations or organisations, language skills, information on former professional experience or practice, hobbies, picture, payment details, IP address, location and other data provided by you voluntarily when you use our services (i.e., when creating your CV, Cover letter or Personal website).

Testimonials: We display personal testimonials of customers on our website. With your consent, we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us [hello@kickresume.com](mailto:hello@kickresume.com).

Personal data provided by you are only visible to you; the Controller doesn't publish your personal data. Upon your own discretion, you can decide to publish your personal data.

  4. #### Storage period

The Controller stores your personal data for 5 years from your last log in.

  5. #### Instruction regarding the voluntariness of provision of your personal data

    1. You provide your personal data voluntarily and it is only up to you to decide, which personal data you will disclose. The CV will only contain the information provided by you. You are entitled to change or delete your personal data entered into the online platform anytime.

    2. Certain functions of the portal are only accessible to users logged-in through their social network account or email.

  6. #### Recipients

The Controller uses cookies and other party applications which are getting basic data (email, IP, number of visits…) and anonymised data about users based on user’s consent. Examples: Google Analytics, Intercom online chat, Paypal. Full list of other parties (recipients) cookies and applications of which we use is listed under this Privacy policy.

The Controller may provide your resume or cover letter on the basis of your consent to the following categories of recipients: (i) partner employers and/or (ii) job recruitment agencies, with which the Controller has concluded an agreement, for the purposes of approaching you with job offers. The Controller has taken the appropriate contractual and organisational measures to ensure that such recipients processes your personal data only in order to approach you with job offers you might be interested in. You always have the right to withdraw this consent by sending an email to: [hello@kickresume.com](mailto:hello@kickresume.com).

  7. #### Disclosure of the Personal Data

The Controller does not publish your personal data.

  8. #### Third Countries

The Controller may transfer your personal data to third countries, i.e., countries that are not member states of the European Union or a party to the Agreement on the European Economic Area where we engage with external service providers. In such case, we transfer your personal data only to a country that are considered to have an adequate level of protection in accordance with the EU Commission's decision or there are appropriate safeguards in place to protect your personal data, such as standard contract clauses, binding internal company rules or US Privacy Shield. Regardless of the country in which your personal data is processed, the Controller takes reasonable technical, legal and organisational measures to ensure that the level of protection is the same as in the European Union and the European Economic Area. If you wish to know more about international transfers of your personal data and the appropriate safeguards that we have in place to govern the transfer of your personal data, you may contact us via hello@kickresume.com.

  9. #### Rights

    1. We hereby notify you that pursuant to the Act, you are have the following rights:

      1. You have a right of access to your personal data we process. This means you can contact us and request from us a confirmation whether or not your personal data are being processed and if so, you have the right to request access to your data, which we will provide to you in the form of a so-called "registry" (stating, in particular, purposes, categories of personal data, categories of recipients of personal data, storage periods or criteria for determining storage periods).
      2. You have the right to have inaccurate personal data we have stored about you rectified
      3. You may also ask us to erase your personal data from our systems. We will comply with such request unless we have a legitimate ground to not delete your personal data.
      4. You have the right to object to processing that is based on a legitimate interest of ours if you have personal reasons that relate to the situation. We may however continue to process your information, despite your objection to the processing, if we have compelling legitimate reasons for the processing that outweigh your privacy interest. Where your personal data are processed for direct marketing purposes, you have the right to object at any time to processing of your personal data for such marketing, which includes profiling to the extent that it is related to such direct marketing.
      5. You may request us to restrict certain processing of your personal data.
      6. You have the right to receive your personal data from us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format in order to transmit the personal data to another controller.
    2. As the data subject, you are also entitled to lodge a complaint with the Office for Personal Data Protection of the Slovak Republic, should you have a suspicion that your personal data are processed unlawfully.

    3. If you do not possess full legal capacity, your rights can be exercised by your statutory representative.

  10. #### Form of the Assertion of your Rights

    1. You can exercise your rights:

      1. in writing, whereas it must be clear from your application that you are asserting your claim; the application filed via email or fax must be delivered to the Controller in writing within three (3) days following its dispatch at the latest;
      2. in person in a verbal form recorded in minutes, whereby it must be clear who asserts the claim, what is the content of the claim and when and by whom the minutes have been executed; the minutes must contain the signature of the person, who have executed the minutes as well as you’re your signature; the Controller is obliged to provide you with a copy of the minutes.
  11. #### Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Kickresume does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 16. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 16, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. Accordingly, children under the age of 16 may only use the service with the permission and supervision of their parents.

  12. #### How we protect your information?

Kickresume’s top priority is protecting your privacy and data, but we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Kickresume or guarantee that your information on the Kickresume may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of any of our industry standard physical, technical or managerial safeguards. When you enter your data we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). No method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. We use a credit card processing company to bill you if you purchase services. This company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes. If you have any questions feel free to contact us at [hello@kickresume.com](mailto:hello@kickresume.com).

  13. #### Data Protection Officer

Kickresume s.r.o. has a **"Data Protection Officer"** who is responsible for matter relating to privacy and data protection. This Data Protection Officer can be reached at following address:

Martin Kosír, Klariská 14, 81103 Bratislava, Slovakia, [hello@kickresume.com](mailto:hello@kickresume.com?subject=DPO)

  14. #### Declaration of the User 

By using kickresume.com I declare that I have been informed of the processing of my personal data and my rights and I agree to receive newsletters to my email address.

All changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page. When we change the policy, we will let you know via email and/or a notice on our Site.

This policy was last modified on June 24, 2019.

### List of recipients

Recipients | Purpose | Data | Country of processing  
---|---|---|---  
Amazon Web Services, Inc. | Infrastructure as a service | All customer data (content, contact, purchase, technical) | Ireland  
Google, Inc.  | User analytics and Advertising | Contact data, purchase data, user behaviour | USA  
Hellobar LLC | User analytics | Contact data | USA  
iKros a.s. | Accounting | Contact data, purchase data | Slovakia  
Intercom, Inc. | Onboarding and support | All customer data | USA, UK, Ireland  
Invelity, s.r.o. | Accounting | Contact data, purchase data | Slovakia  
Linode, LLC | Infrastructure as a service, hosting | All customer data (content, contact, purchase, technical) | Germany  
Mixpanel, Inc. | User analytics | User behaviour analytics | USA  
Microsoft Corporation | Advertising | User behaviour | USA  
OMEGA | Accounting | Contact data, purchase data | Slovakia  
Paypal Holdings, Inc. | Payments | Contact data, purchase data, payment data | USA  
Pymetrics, Inc. | Job Advisor feature | Contact data | USA  
Sparkpost | Email management | Contact data | USA  
SUMO | Pop-up | Social media data | USA  
Tapfiliate | Affiliate advertising | Analytics | Ireland  
200 OK, LLC (ProfitWell) | Payment analytics | Contact data, purchase data | USA  
Hotjar Ltd | User analytics | User behaviour analytics | Malta  
  
This privacy policy is also available in Slovak language.
